Joe Binns



Junior gameplay programmer excited about innovating.

I'm a physics-oriented gameplay programmer with experience in both Unity (6 years) and Unreal C++ (1 year). Nearing the end of my studies at Futuregames, I'm **seeking internships starting**January 2024.

Employment

Study Support Mentor @ Lund University

March 2021 — June 2022 · Lund, SE

Provided one-to-one tailored mentoring for BSc students at the Department of Physics.

Unity Developer Intern @ MLabs

July 2019 — August 2019 · London, UK

Lead development on a realistic, real-time 3D urban environment simulation, for use by an automated transport planning system.

Education

YH Game Programmer @ Futuregames

August 2022 — December 2024 · Stockholm, SE Specialised in gameplay programming and technical art.

BSc Theoretical Physics @ Lund University

March 2021 — June 2022 · Lund, SE

Thesis was written on the topic of Combined Regularisation Techniques for Artificial Neural Networks.

Contact

joebinns.com

Joe Binns

i joebinns

<u>(+46) 73 462 47 49</u>

Sweden & UK

Technical Skills

Programming Fluency

C#, Python, Javascript, C++, Java, LaTeX, HTML and CSS.

Libraries

Tensorflow, Three.js, LWJGL, Forge Networking and Mapbox.

Tools

Git, Perforce, Unity, Unreal, Blender and Photoshop.

Select Project

★Stylised Character
Controller

Joe Binns 1